supernewss.com 2013-05-17

# Privacy Policy | SuperNewss.com

Privacy Policy for http://supernewss.com  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to  
contact us by using the form on this page: Contact.

At http://supernewss.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This  
privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by  
http://supernewss.com and how it is used.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites,http://supernewss.com makes use of log files. The information  
inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service  
Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends,  
administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP  
addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons

http://supernewss.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences,  
record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content  
based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

• Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://supernewss.com  
• Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://supernewss.com and other sites on the Internet.  
• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network  
privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising  
partners include ….  
• Google Adsense  
• Commission Junction  
• Adbrite  
• Clickbank  
• Azoogle  
• Amazon  
• Neverblue

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that  
appear on http://supernewss.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive  
your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

http://supernewss.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by  
third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad  
servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out  
of certain practices. http://supernewss.com ’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we  
cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed  
information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’  
respective websites.
